<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:45:42 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Excited</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/ninth-blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:45:42 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/ninth-blog/</guid><description>School starts back up in one week I am excited and nervous about it. I will have a lot more to write about once school starts up because I will be taking C# 2, Javascript, Security Fundamentals and writing 101. These are all classes that will make me a better developer so I am super excited to continue my coding journey and working with Carol on some new things and ideas that I will have.</description></item><item><title>Docker Database Migrations</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/eighth-blog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 08:27:51 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/eighth-blog/</guid><description>After finishing my docker-compose file to connect MySQL database to the flask app I ran into another problem with creating the database tables, I thought this would be a straight forward thing to do and apparently it is not from all the research I have done on the issue so far. I will continue to document everything I try, what works and what does not, hopefully it will help someone with similar issues.</description></item><item><title>Git Submodules</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/seventh-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 16:15:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/seventh-blog/</guid><description>Today I was able to fix both of my problems I was having. The first one with creating a docker image with my flask app I was able to use a different python image from docker hub that was not labeled with &amp;ldquo;-alpine&amp;rdquo;, after that the build went successfully. My second issue was not being able to serve my hugo blogs web pages locally, I was able to fix this by going into the themes folder and running &amp;ldquo;git submodule init&amp;rdquo; &amp;amp; &amp;ldquo;git submodule update&amp;rdquo; which this actually solves two problems for me now I can get to the themes files so I should be able to add some CSS and style some of my pages the way I want to.</description></item><item><title>Programmers Award</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/awards/awards3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 20:26:41 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/awards/awards3/</guid><description>I was awarded a certified programmers certificate for my programming skills while attending Jefferson Community College.</description></item><item><title>Deans List</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/awards/awards2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 20:24:43 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/awards/awards2/</guid><description>I made the Deans list for the spring semester of 2022 while attending Jefferson Community College.</description></item><item><title>docker build errors</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/sixth-blog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 15:48:42 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/sixth-blog/</guid><description>I ran into a problem when building my docker image for my flask_app. When installing the requirements.txt file it breaks when it gets to pyscopg2, I tried to install the pyscopg2-binary because that seemed to work on another project when I ran into a similar problem but that did not work. I also updated Ubuntu on my desktop computer and the Hugo server is not working properly after that update. I will continue to document my progress and these are all things that are learning experiences.</description></item><item><title>Learning new things</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/fifth-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 12:30:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/fifth-blog/</guid><description>I was able to solve the linked list problem on hacker rank and it was nowhere near as hard as I thought it was going to be. Although the way they set the problem up was a little different than any problem I seen when researching how linked list work in python. I also am trying to network with people more that way I can get different perspectives on things and see how other people solve the same problem.</description></item><item><title>Linked List</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/fourth-blog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 20:40:55 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/fourth-blog/</guid><description>Today I looked at my next problem to solve for 30 Days of Code on Hacker Rank and it is a Linked List problem this is all new to me and I am having a little trouble with it. I need to complete an insert functionso that it creates a new node and inserts it at the tail of the linked list refrenced by the head parameter. I think this will be the hardest problem to solve that I have had so far but after some research on the subject I am sure I will be able to solve it.</description></item><item><title>Certifications</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/third-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 18:52:47 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/third-blog/</guid><description>Today I added my certifications to my blog. I am trying to figure out how to add color to the text to kind of give it little style to my page so far everything I have read and tried has been unsuccessful. I have also been reading through Django&amp;rsquo;s documentation to try and get a better understanding of how to use the Django framework.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio Setup</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/second-blog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 15:46:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/second-blog/</guid><description>Today I added some content to my portfolio. I have really been working hard on building projects to add to my portfolio and I am really happy with the result. This new blog using hugo is has really made things a lot easier for me to write and publish my content.</description></item><item><title>certifications</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/certifications/certs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:02:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/certifications/certs/</guid><description>PC Pro Certified Build, Troubleshoot, &amp;amp; repair PC&amp;rsquo;s Net+ Pro Certified Configure, troubleshoot, and repair networks for home or office network setups.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/about/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 14:57:30 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/about/about/</guid><description>this is the about page</description></item><item><title>First Blog</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/first-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 17:25:46 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/blog/first-blog/</guid><description>Welcome everyone to my blog! I hope you enjoy it. I will try to write in this as much as possible and share my journey with you.</description></item><item><title>Deans List</title><link>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/awards/awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:00:39 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://kquiggins.github.io/hugo_blog/awards/awards/</guid><description>I made the Deans list for the spring and fall semesters of 2021 while attending Jefferson Community College.</description></item></channel></rss>